{
  "RC": [
    {
      "Passage": "In the past, credit for telling the tale of Aladdin has often gone to Antoine Galland . . . the first European translator of . . . Arabian Nights [which] started as a series of translations of an incomplete manuscript of a medieval Arabic story collection. . . But, though those tales were of medieval origin, Aladdin may be a more recent invention. Scholars have not found a manuscript of the story that predates the version published in 1712 by Galland, who wrote in his diary that he first heard the tale from a Syrian storyteller from Aleppo named Hanna Diyab . . .\n\nDespite the fantastical elements of the story, scholars now think the main character may actually be based on a real person’s real experiences. . . . Though Galland never credited Diyab in his published translations of the Arabian Nights stories, Diyab wrote something of his own: a travelogue penned in the mid-18th century. In it, he recalls telling Galland the story of Aladdin [and] describes his own hard-knocks upbringing and the way he marveled at the extravagance of Versailles. The descriptions he uses were very similar to the descriptions of the lavish palace that ended up in Galland’s version of the Aladdin story. [Therefore, author Paulo Lemos] Horta believes that “Aladdin might be the young Arab Maronite from Aleppo, marveling at the jewels and riches of Versailles.” . . .\n\nFor 300 years, scholars thought that the rags-to-riches story of Aladdin might have been inspired by the plots of French fairy tales that came out around the same time, or that the story was invented in that 18th century period as a byproduct of French Orientalism, a fascination with stereotypical exotic Middle Eastern luxuries that was prevalent then. The idea that Diyab might have based it on his own life — the experiences of a Middle Eastern man encountering the French, not vice-versa — flips the script. [According to Horta,] “Diyab was ideally placed to embody the overlapping world of East and West, blending the storytelling traditions of his homeland with his youthful observations of the wonder of 18th-century France.” . . .\nTo the scholars who study the tale, its narrative drama isn’t the only reason storytellers keep finding reason to return to Aladdin. It reflects not only “a history of the French and the Middle East, but also [a story about] Middle Easterners coming to Paris and that speaks to our world today,” as Horta puts it. “The day Diyab told the story of Aladdin to Galland, there were riots due to food shortages during the winter and spring of 1708 to 1709, and Diyab was sensitive to those people in a way that Galland is not. When you read this diary, you see this solidarity among the Arabs who were in Paris at the time. . . . There is little in the writings of Galland that would suggest that he was capable of developing a character like Aladdin with sympathy, but Diyab’s memoir reveals a narrator adept at capturing the distinctive psychology of a young protagonist, as well as recognizing the kinds of injustices and opportunities that can transform the path of any youthful adventurer.",
      "Q1": {
        "Question": "All of the following serve as evidence for the character of Aladdin being based on Hanna Diyab EXCEPT:",
        "O1": "Diyab’s cosmopolitanism and cross-cultural experience.",
        "O2": "Diyab’s humble origins and class struggles, as recounted in his travelogue.",
        "O3": "Diyab’s description of the wealth of Versailles in his travelogue.",
        "O4": "Diyab’s narration of the original story to Galland.",
        "Answer": "4"
      },
      "Q2": {
        "Question": "The author of the passage is most likely to agree with which of the following explanations for the origins of the story of Aladdin?",
        "O1": "Galland derived the story of Aladdin from Diyab’s travelogue in which he recounts his fascination with the wealth of Versailles.",
        "O2": "The story of Aladdin has its origins in an undiscovered, incomplete manuscript of a medieval Arabic collection of stories.",
        "O3": "Basing it on his own life experiences, Diyab transmitted the story of Aladdin to Galland who included it in Arabian Nights.",
        "O4": "Galland received the story of Aladdin from Diyab who, in turn, found it in an incomplete medieval manuscript.",
        "Answer": "3"
      },
      "Q3": {
        "Question": "Which of the following, if true, would invalidate the inversion that the phrase “flips the script” refers to?",
        "O1": "Diyab’s travelogue described the affluence of the French city of Bordeaux, instead of Versailles.",
        "O2": "The French fairy tales of the eighteenth century did not have rags-to-riches plot lines like that of the tale of Aladdin.",
        "O3": "The description of opulence in Hanna Diyab’s and Antoine Galland’s narratives bore no resemblance to each other.",
        "O4": "Galland acknowledged in the published translations of Arabian Nights that he heard the story of Aladdin from Diyab.",
        "Answer": "3"
      },
      "Q4": {
        "Question": "Which of the following is the primary reason for why storytellers are still fascinated by the story of Aladdin?",
        "O1": "The traveller's experience that inspired the tale of Aladdin resonates even today.",
        "O2": "The tale of Aladdin documents the history of Europe and Middle East.",
        "O3": "The archetype of the rags-to-riches story of Aladdin makes it popular even today.",
        "O4": "The story of Aladdin is evidence of the eighteenth century French Orientalist.",
        "Answer": "1"
      },
      "Q5": {
        "Question": "Which of the following does not contribute to the passage’s claim about the authorship of Aladdin?",
        "O1": "The narrative sensibility of Diyab’s travelogue.",
        "O2": "The depiction of the affluence of Versailles in Diyab’s travelogue.",
        "O3": "Galland’s acknowledgment of Diyab in his diary.",
        "O4": "The story-line of many French fairy tales of the 18th century.",
        "Answer": "4"
      }
    },
    {
      "Passage": "Contemporary internet shopping conjures a perfect storm of choice anxiety. Research has consistently held that people who are presented with a few options make better, easier decisions than those presented with many. . . . Helping consumers figure out what to buy amid an endless sea of choice online has become a cottage industry unto itself. Many brands and retailers now wield marketing buzzwords such as curation, differentiation, and discovery as they attempt to sell an assortment of stuff targeted to their ideal customer. Companies find such shoppers through the data gold mine of digital advertising, which can catalog people by gender, income level, personal interests, and more. Since Americans have lost the ability to sort through the sheer volume of the consumer choices available to them, a ghost now has to be in the retail machine, whether it’s an algorithm, an influencer, or some snazzy ad tech to help a product follow you around the internet. Indeed, choice fatigue is one reason so many people gravitate toward lifestyle influencers on Instagram—the relentlessly chic young moms and perpetually vacationing 20-somethings—who present an aspirational worldview, and then recommend the products and services that help achieve it. . . .\n\nFor a relatively new class of consumer-products start-ups, there’s another method entirely. Instead of making sense of a sea of existing stuff, these companies claim to disrupt stuff as Americans know it. Casper (mattresses), Glossier (makeup), Away (suitcases), and many others have sprouted up to offer consumers freedom from choice: The companies have a few aesthetically pleasing and supposedly highly functional options, usually at mid-range prices. They’re selling nice things, but maybe more importantly, they’re selling a confidence in those things, and an ability to opt out of the stuff rat race. . . .\n\nOne-thousand-dollar mattresses and $300 suitcases might solve choice anxiety for a certain tier of consumer, but the companies that sell them, along with those that attempt to massage the larger stuff economy into something navigable, are still just working within a consumer market that’s broken in systemic ways. The presence of so much stuff in America might be more valuable if it were more evenly distributed, but stuff’s creators tend to focus their energy on those who already have plenty. As options have expanded for people with disposable income, the opportunity to buy even basic things such as fresh food or quality diapers has contracted for much of America’s lower classes.\n\nFor start-ups that promise accessible simplicity, their very structure still might eventually push them toward overwhelming variety. Most of these companies are based on hundreds of millions of dollars of venture capital, the investors of which tend to expect a steep growth rate that can’t be achieved by selling one great mattress or one great sneaker. Casper has expanded into bedroom furniture and bed linens. Glossier, after years of marketing itself as no-makeup makeup that requires little skill to apply, recently launched a full line of glittering color cosmetics. There may be no way to opt out of stuff by buying into the right thing.",
      "Q1": {
        "Question": "Which of the following hypothetical statements would add the least depth to the author’s prediction of the fate of start-ups offering few product options?",
        "O1": "An exponential surge in their sales enables start-ups to meet their desired profit goals without expanding their product catalogue",
        "O2": "With the motive of promoting certain rival companies, the government decides to double the tax-rates for these start-ups.",
        "O3": "With Casper and Glossier venturing into new product ranges, their regular customers start losing trust in the companies and their products.",
        "O4": "Start-ups with few product options are no exception to the American consumer market that is deeply divided along class lines.",
        "Answer": "1"
      },
      "Q2": {
        "Question": "Which one of the following best sums up the overall purpose of the examples of Casper and Glossier in the passage?",
        "O1": "They are increasing the purchasing power of poor Americans.",
        "O2": "They are exceptions to a dominant trend in consumer markets.",
        "O3": "They are facilitating a uniform distribution of commodities in the market.",
        "O4": "They might transform into what they were exceptions to.",
        "Answer": "4"
      },
      "Q3": {
        "Question": "They might transform into what they were exceptions to.",
        "O1": "A range of 10 products priced between $5 and $10.",
        "O2": "A range of 25 products priced between $10 and $25.",
        "O3": "A range of 25 products priced between $5 and $10.",
        "O4": "A range of 10 products priced between $10 and $25.",
        "Answer": "1"
      },
      "Q4": {
        "Question": "All of the following, IF TRUE, would weaken the author’s claims EXCEPT:",
        "O1": "product options increased market competition, bringing down the prices of commodities, which, in turn, increased purchasing power of the poor.",
        "O2": "the annual sales growth of companies with fewer product options were higher than that of companies which curated their products for target consumers.",
        "O3": "the annual sale of companies that hired lifestyle influencers on Instagram for marketing their products were 40% less than those that did not.",
        "O4": "the empowerment felt by purchasers in buying a commodity were directly proportional to the number of options they could choose from.",
        "Answer": "2"
      },
      "Q5": {
        "Question": "Based on the passage, all of the following can be inferred about consumer behaviour EXCEPT that:",
        "O1": "too many options have made it difficult for consumers to trust products.",
        "O2": "consumers are susceptible to marketing images that they see on social media.",
        "O3": "having too many product options can be overwhelming for consumers.",
        "O4": "consumers tend to prefer products by start-ups over those by established companies.",
        "Answer": "4"
      }
    }
  ]
}